[MUSIC PLAYING]
In the not too distant future, somewhere in time and space,
Mike Nelson and his robot pals are caught in an endless chase.
Pursued by a woman whose name is Pearl, an evil gal who
wants to rule the world.
She threw a few things in her purse.
And in her rocket ship, she hunts him
all across the universe.
I'll get you!
I'll send him cheesy movies, the worst I can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all, and I'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind Mike can't control
where the movies begin or end.
He'll try to keep his sanity with the help
of his robot friends.
Robot rules called Kebab.
You're on.
Cheesy.
Smile.
Don't servo.
Check me out.
I am ripped.
You've been wondering how he eats and breathes
and other science facts.
Just repeat to yourself, it's just a show.
You should really just relax.
Oh, Mystery Science Theater 3000.
[THUNDER]
Hi, everyone.
Mike Nelson here.
Just want to make sure we're all caught up.
See, we've become unstuck in time,
and currently we're shipwrecked over Earth's orbit
in the year 2525, a time where--
a time where apes rule the world and man has been--
hey, crow, I'm doing a thing here, huh?
Sorry, Mike.
Turns out the satellite's infested with prairie dogs.
Uh-huh.
Yep, they're tunneling damages irrigation systems,
and the beefalo can break their legs in the hole.
But, crow, we don't have any--
Have a good solution to the prairie dog problem?
That's why I got this little beauty out of Barment Master
magazine.
It's much more humane than poison and much more efficient,
and we can relocate our catch or chop them up and feed them
to the black-footed ferret, their mortal enemy.
But, crow, we don't have any prairie dogs.
Oh, got one.
OK, sir, I'm going to bring him through.
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, missy.
We'll be right back then.
[barking]
Oh, hi.
[music playing]
Hey, crow.
How you doing?
Sarbo, the guy that changed the rugs, is here.
Crow, why can't you remember me?
I saw you five minutes ago when you were vacuuming prairie dogs
out of the satellite.
Oh, I was vacuuming prairie dogs.
OK, sure.
Sarbo!
Never mind.
The apes are calling anyway.
Yeah, I'm sure in whatever feverish dream world you live in,
apes are calling a lot.
Woo!
Vacuum it back!
Now, peanuts!
[barking]
Is there anything we can help you with today?
Yes, in fact, I--
I'm doing--
[growling]
Yes, in accordance with the lawgiver,
I must do some fact checking about your experiment.
Now, first, have you noticed any more weight gain
or any change in the hundreds of moles on your skin?
No, I think--
Hey.
Has your hairless pink skin remained clammy and moist,
or is there less musky oil and sweat?
I think there's been more, Mike.
Yeah, tell them about the feet too, Mike.
Please keep your dolls quiet.
I must finish this before the lawgiver arrives.
Now, has the flaking on your malformed head been steady,
or is it more of a--
[laughing]
Good heavens, ape!
What are you doing?
I feel so free!
Don't leave, Professor Bobo!
Now, stop it!
Stop it this instant!
Have you no sense of dignity, ape!
No!
This is what we were meant for!
Do it!
You're right!
This is wonderful!
I'm a monkey, damn it, a monkey!
And I'm wearing a diaper, Dr. Peanut!
Yes, and not because you have to.
They're just more convenient!
[laughing]
The lawgiver had just--
was taking off my damn shoe-toes.
Clean yourselves up.
Your movie this week is Leech Woman, and it's--
I confuse a lot of these.
I just know myself.
No.
Ew, I'm--
Movie time!
I'm gonna spit in the ocean.
The Earth has male-pattern baldness.
[laughing]
The Sean Young saga.
Get the salt.
Lot of salt.
Starring these leeches.
Colleen Thorax Gray and Grant.
See how he sticks to the side of the aquarium, Williams.
And the Leech family singers.
Wow, there's a lot of hair in the gate.
The music can't really get into it here.
You know, in spite of all this, I'm left cold and empty.
That's the runway system for the Minneapolis-St. Paul Airport
in a couple years.
And Lee Merriweather.
Ah, it's a Rorschach test.
I see a lot of spilled ink, congealing, and random patterns.
That means you're a sexual predator.
I think.
Ed Gein?
Oh, oh.
You be Blake.
And it's so embarrassing to have to report your own death.
Let's see, tattooing, body piercing, yeah.
Okay, I threw my endocrine back in Toma.
Endocrinologist and tanning.
Yes, I'm Paul Talbot, endocrinologist extraordinaire.
It's five alive.
Well, that's a nice one.
Five.
Well, that's a novelty.
You're refusing anything with alcohol in it.
Wow.
I'm used to seeing you sober this time of day.
You're trying to humiliate me.
You did that years ago.
Everybody knows I drink.
I don't try to hide it.
Does he insult all those patients?
Drinking.
My feelings for you are both bad for me.
I know that.
What can I do?
You can quit pawing my recipe box.
I can't reach you without crawling into the bottle.
It's a tight fit, believe me.
And when I'm there, I can at least pretend that you love me.
Still not my line.
Do not act.
And that our marriage is what a marriage is supposed to be.
It's interesting to watch a bottle baby defend her weakness.
One thing I can say for you, your approach is always different.
Today it's complete submission.
I can't even get a rise out of you.
Likewise.
You know, I think I like you better when you're sloppy, drunk, and violent.
You mean it?
That's the real you and that's the one I like.
The one that hates me and gives me a chance to hate back.
It's too much baby because that's all your worth.
Now, that's when we're at our best.
When we cut through the superficial surface and get down to the fact that we're a cruddy pair,
the only difference is I know what I am.
And you.
You minx.
You try to hide what you are in the fumes of whiskey.
Did you say whiskey?
See, I blame this on the HMOs.
It's a pile of beef or booze.
You need this urine sample?
Ew.
Would you please just take the birth control pamphlets and go?
Here's to you, whiskey.
Why, thank you.
The guardian of all frustrated wives.
Defender of truth, friend to children.
Now, be a good girl and take your guardian and go home.
I've got some experimenting to do.
This week on WB, the sarcastic endocrinologist.
You know, I don't like to be distracted when I'm working.
Unless, of course, you've changed your mind about helping me with my experiments.
You need more than me to be successful in whatever you do.
Wait.
Just go on butchering your guinea pigs.
I can't put you in jail for that.
Now, act.
As a doctor, I resent the word butchering almost as much as I resent looking at you.
Yikes.
I don't know why you came here today, but whatever it was, speak up and then get out.
Schedule an ermine removal with a receptionist.
You know something?
I've just decided to do you a big favor.
I'm gonna paint your house.
I'm going to give you that divorce so you won't have to look at my face any longer.
And don't forget, Nick and Honey are coming over tonight.
Tried making it over for you.
Nope.
Not in the scene.
Plastic surgery can't bridge that ten years between us.
Sorry, not in the scene.
Only love could make you look at me differently.
And booze.
And you never had that.
Not even in the beginning.
Do you have any pretzels?
Uh, you're getting sloppy.
Another couple of drinks and you're liable to forget about the divorce.
And we'll be right back where we started from.
Go on home.
Call Neil and tell him to start the proceedings.
Tell him to use any grounds, whatever he wants.
Just let him get on with it.
And stop acting.
You got what you want?
Why can't I have a little one for the road?
Just enough to make me numb.
Mm-hmm. Would you like to supersize it?
This is when Hazelton didn't have it all worked out yet.
Right.
I'd like to announce the engagement of me and Johnny Walker.
God, they should just put booze in squeeze bottles, huh?
And now a moment of silence for booze gone by.
Do you want me to take a look at that boil now, ma'am?
I think I did it.
Today's miracle cure, booze!
I can't feel anything.
Inside or out.
He's a doctor of assisted alcoholism.
Well, I guess I'll just go throw up on the receptionist.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Yeah, lady, let's go.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Doctor, there's someone in the office to see you.
Oh, that's all right, Sally.
Mrs. Talbot was just leaving.
Yes, I...
I was just leaving.
Oh, is she just leaving?
Finally.
Prepare a vodka poultice for our next patient.
I know you advertise for old women,
but the one in the office looks like she came right out of a mummy's tomb.
I told her that, too.
There's something peculiar about her.
She gives me the creeps.
It's like she's old or something.
Old women always give me the creeps.
Except Carol Channing.
But remember, it's worth millions if I can ever find a way to make them young again.
Shall I show her in?
Yes, but first get rid of that glass and that bottle.
I'll just finish it up. How about that?
Deal?
I'm on my way home now.
Can you meet me there in about 30 minutes?
Oh, God, yeah.
Do you have any readers' digest?
No.
I had an affair with Lincoln, you know?
Everything's the same.
Chad!
Pretty and all.
Oh, Otis Nixon's twin sister.
Goodbye.
I wonder if there are any drive-through liquor stores on the way home.
Finally, we're leaving.
Yeah, let's get out of this place.
Mrs. Talbot.
Have you tried Phillips?
You will never divorce your husband.
He won't have to.
He will die.
Mother, please.
Death will give you life.
A new way of life.
You may run away, but you will never escape me.
You are the one in my dreams of blood.
But everyone's in my dreams of blood, so it's not that big a deal.
Oh, why do I push people away?
So, those are my dreams of blood.
Wild, huh?
Well, the tests came back, and it turns out you're old.
Fair.
That's all.
By the way, you give the doctor and me the creeps.
You know, if old women give them the creeps, maybe you shouldn't have gone into old womanology.
Wait, what's this shrunken apple doll doing in my...
Oh, gee.
God, even your atoms are disgusting.
It's remarkable.
Carpizole count, blood pressure, teeth all indicate extreme old age.
And yet she's only in her late two hundreds.
Could you help her up?
I'd be tempted to believe you if you had a birth certificate.
Or a major credit card.
That is my birth certificate.
The brand of the Arab slaver who stole me and my mother from Africa
and sold us across the sea 140 years ago.
140 years ago?
140 years ago.
My mother comforted me.
I learned much from her.
Things that you'd want to know.
What things?
Decoupage.
When we are alone, I will speak.
Well, we kind of are alone.
Nursey isn't the sharpest knife in the drawer.
Nurse looks like she backed up over her own hair.
Sally, would you mind?
But I'm young.
Darling.
Now what did you learn from your mother that you think could be of value to me?
I am of the Nando people who once lived in Tonganika beyond the Colombo Falls.
Outside Pittsburgh?
I thought they were all dead, but now I hear that many of my tribes still live deep in the wilderness.
I want to go to them.
You will give me the money to go.
Why should I do that?
Are you not trying to find a way to get to the Nando people?
I'm not trying to find a way to go to them.
Why should I do that?
Are you not trying to find a way to make the old young again?
Only to make them younger.
Nothing can reverse the aging process.
Nothing that you would know about.
You dissing me?
Help me down, please.
I'm going to put on a dashiki and blow your mind.
Just let me get out my coffee coupon here.
This is all that remains of my inheritance.
A few pinches of the life-giving nipie.
Or Mike Copenhagen.
My mother left me.
Nipie? What is it?
I don't know.
All I know is that it has kept me alive many years beyond my time.
And looking great.
I would be young again. I must return to my people.
This is a ketchup packet from Denny's.
Are you saying this powder will make you young again?
No.
Oh, gee.
They slowly approach a death.
There's another substance that must be mixed with it to make one young.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know what it is.
A big surprise.
It's the secret of the high priest of Nandos.
And a lady at my high rise also knows.
I'm a man of science.
I don't pay for mumbo jumbo.
I won't take any more of your time.
You can get your coat.
Then return the night pay.
Yeah, girl.
There are other scientists.
One might even ask for a demonstration before he tells me to go.
Hmm.
A demonstration?
Mm-hmm.
Get me a glass of water.
And a hard boiled egg and a piece of string.
I'm afraid all I've got is whiskey.
Is that all right?
You know, he's a master of not acting.
He's got built-in smug.
All of the glass is all spotty, but I guess I'll drink it anyway.
It's Flava-Rite brand night pay.
Who's that, Dick Butkus on there?
Oh, that's good night pay.
Now we must wait a few minutes and then you can examine me again.
You devil.
And you will see for yourself that the night pay hasn't slowed the aging process.
All right, I'll run the tests again.
But I won't like it.
This powder does as you say.
You'll have all the money you need to return to your people.
Hmm.
Do I trust him?
What do you folks at home think?
I'll be right back.
Well, have you tried another mixer?
Hey, look, she has an original Ray Kroc on the wall.
This isn't a very good slumber party, Susan.
I'm sorry.
I was going to get you a drink and I got held up over by the bar.
Our drink special tonight is You Stand By Me and I Breathe.
Of course you don't have to buy the vacuum cleaner.
Mrs. Talbot, I know this is painful,
but it's one of those things that have to be done when you plan a divorce.
You have to be married.
Now you and Paul own everything jointly, is that right?
Well...
Then let's start with the front.
Could you set a value on it?
Oh, I'd say it's worth about 400 gear minutes.
It's trash.
Hmm?
Everything's trash.
Except for the Zetith high-five.
It'll make a difference to you later on, believe me.
Everything makes a difference.
It's all trash.
Open wide, Dino.
Well, thank you very much.
Like me.
Old trash.
I think you've had it for tonight.
You get some sleep.
No.
I'll take you up to your room.
No, I don't want you to go.
Mrs. Talbot, please.
No, please don't leave me alone.
Mrs. Talbot.
No, no.
You know something?
I'm going to blow.
You know what she said?
That I had been drinking.
She said, "You are the one in my dreams of blood."
Yeah, she says that to everybody.
That's what she said.
I'm going to get you a doctor.
You're drinking yourself into the deep cheese.
I don't want to.
Now, come on.
I don't need a doctor.
Sit down here while I...
I don't want a doctor.
Neil, I'm glad you're here.
You're just the man I wanted to see.
I'd like to take a look at your endocrine.
Since I'm representing your wife,
don't you think it'd be more ethical
if you got another attorney?
What for?
Your divorce.
Divorce?
Who said anything about a divorce?
Come, both of you.
Let's go to the bar.
I've got a story to tell you that's fantastic.
The bar?
Are we there yet?
Sit down.
What am I going to do to get a drink around here?
Come on, come on!
I want to show you my Mexican jumping beans.
You're looking at the most powerful
concentrate of hormone known,
a hormone that retards aging.
Now, a similar hormone was first discovered
in insects by a British biologist 20, 25 years ago.
Common silkworm produces it.
The only trouble with that hormone is
it works only in insects.
This...
Finger.
Works in humans.
It's kept a woman living more than twice
her normal span of life.
She's 152 years old, Neil.
She was in my office this afternoon.
152 years old?
I've confirmed it.
I've counted her rings.
Where did she get this?
A plant that comes from Africa.
Now, she also mentioned another substance
which, when mixed with this,
Creamy no-guy.
will actually make old people young again.
But really, only women need it.
Paul, you talk as if you believe this was possible.
I do.
Enough to go to Africa to try to find a source.
Hi, have you been helped?
June, I want you to come with me.
Gee, I'm not sure. Okay.
I didn't think you could forgive all those awful things
I said to you this afternoon.
June, I need you.
You've got to help.
I can't do it alone.
You mean you don't want a divorce?
Of course not.
I'll make it all up to you.
Oh, what an idiot I've been,
not to realize how important you are to me.
So I guess I'll just be, uh...
The trip together...
I'm just gonna go...
The new country, the jungle, it'll be so exciting.
You parked me in.
Paul, you're my life.
You and Boots.
You just pulled me out of the bottom of the pit.
My self-esteem is in your hands.
If you ever let me go again,
it'll be the end of everything for me.
Darling, I'm sorry.
Darling, don't think of such things.
Just think of our being together...
Codependent some more.
...and how much I love you.
Now get your orthopedic shoes on.
We're going out for pudding.
Blah.
Excuse me.
You are looking live at sold-out Serengeti.
Oh, I love world music.
Sorry the experiment failed, honey.
Yes, I know the nanopeople.
They're a savage, proud race.
They refuse to accept anything from our so-called civilization.
They have an undying hatred for Europeans.
Well, me, anyway.
The government has issued orders to respect their territory
and leave them strictly alone.
So I was told at the consulate.
Then why come to me?
I've heard you're a gambler.
And a rambler, and I guess you always will.
Wait, gamble.
If I don't get killed by the Nandos,
I lose my license as a guide.
So what's to win?
$5,000 now and $20,000 more if I find what I'm after.
That's a lot of wicker.
Doctor, that's a lot of money.
But I'm afraid I cannot do anything for you.
I'm stuck to my chair.
No one can.
How do you know what I'm looking for?
It's obvious.
You haven't said a word about guns or wildlife.
And you're not the first scientist to ask me about the Nandos.
Though you are the oiliest.
That can only mean one thing, doctor.
The legend that they have a secret process to retard age.
Dig this clown.
Doctor Talbot, as much as I would enjoy earning your money,
I cannot help you find something which doesn't exist.
Yeah, great. Here, don't cash us for a laugh.
I'm not asking for your advice or opinion.
I'm merely seeking your services as a guide.
I'm citing you for a comb-over.
Your insistence does not impress me,
but your money is most persuasive.
And your cat checks are adorable.
Doctor, you have got yourself a guide.
Your five dollar down payment is impressive.
Now, come to think of it, about three days ago,
an old Nando woman came through here
and hired bearers to carry her back to her tribe.
Down the wall. Did he bag the Grinch's dog?
Did you see her?
Oh, Max.
No, she was in a litter behind curtains.
Never showed herself.
But I heard she was old.
You know it, Sam.
(Singing)
Then you must be Molly.
You know her?
Yes, yes. And if we could overtake her,
I'm sure we could get a friendly introduction to her people.
(Beeping)
Well, I don't know, Crow.
Your nanites seem like hard workers,
but it doesn't seem like they've had time to fix the ship.
Oh, yeah, you'll see, Mike.
These little guys are great.
There's countless billions of them covering the entire ship,
and they're just so focused that...
(Grunting)
And so it's not surprising that we should allow them
to do anything that we should.
Let's go see what the problem is.
Oh, right. Okay.
Uh, hello? This is Mike. Anybody in there?
Black headquarters. What do you got?
You a union man?
Well, I certainly hope you're not on strike against us,
but we were just wondering how long it would take to fix our ship.
Oh, that job.
Right. Don't worry.
We're not striking you guys.
You're not the problem.
Capitalism's not the problem.
What about your spaceship?
That job had to stop.
We've got a bigger job now, son.
Maybe you've heard about our new job.
It's called building the dignity of the worker.
You don't need a union, they say.
We'll give you a contract, they say.
You know what we say?
We've seen crap.
Tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet, tweet.
So there's no chance that we could get it done, you know,
any time in the next, well, I don't know.
I'd like you to meet an ex-boy, Jody.
He's a preacher.
It were during the union summer the prairie fire started.
Some said they caved that mine in on purpose,
but I couldn't hardly believe it.
Ma told me just to mind myself.
They're coming!
[shouting]
Well, okay, so there's no chance that we could get it done within the next,
you know, week or two we were looking at at the outside, but that's fine.
The Nammites, united, will never be defeated.
Remember us, remember this night, remember Jody!
[laughing]
Fellas, I think we're involved in something bigger than any of us.
You know, one thumb could take care of the whole problem, Mike.
Ah, I better not.
We'll be right back.
Well, still, we'll...
[music]
[
Still, this is better than Congo.
[laughing]
Right on!
Somebody help me down!
Filmed entirely on location at Bachman's Floral.
They glued ears onto him.
[laughing]
Babar in Southern Comfort.
Be careful with my record collection.
Mammy, mammy!
Um, ee oo oo ah ah.
[laughing]
Boy, are they in Africa.
Don't start.
Out of Africa.
No, no, there's more in the trunk.
[laughing]
I've got the Seagrams, the mix is behind me.
Wow, it's a really seamless blending of stock footage.
Well, we'd better camp here tonight.
The next stock footage is 18 miles away.
♪ Going to Montana soon ♪
♪ Gonna be a mental despotic woman ♪
When's dinner, honey? Come on.
[music]
Well, I never...
[birds chirping]
My purse! He took my purse!
[music]
Don Prudhomme.
This guy's been antique hunting and that's about it.
Boy, Africa sucks. Who's for Asia?
[music]
All the matte paintings of Africa are beautiful.
Yeah.
Who now? Good Entmuth.
Who, hum? Hum who?
[music]
Now that's the Colombo. We'll cross over and make for a fall.
Please, I said no pictures, please.
[music]
[speaking African]
Clearly, he speaks African.
[music]
Look at that, look at...
This is gross, even for me.
[music]
Sometimes I feel so fat.
Fire one.
[music]
Did the water just get warmer, Earl?
Boy, it's humid today.
Guess they came to Africa around animal convention time, huh?
[music]
You gotta go, go now.
That's exactly what I want to do with my life.
Well, a lion does not sleep tonight, I'll tell you that.
I don't see what's remotely funny about that.
Now we should be right about there.
And yet we're not.
Another half day's journey will bring us to the falls right here.
We'll cash most of our supplies there and leave...
I enjoy being a blue.
The rest of the carriers we'll send back.
We three go on.
Well, have a good night, Wes.
Night.
Tonight we ride mini bikes and throw hard candy.
[speaking African]
White man, please advise.
Expecting a flood, sir?
Alfred Hitchcock's The Us.
[speaking African]
You know, these Africans just don't understand Africa.
Oh, so anyway, when you're transitioning from a minor seventh,
you may want to use an inverted chord.
Another long day tomorrow. You better get some sleep.
A lot of sleep, if you know what I mean.
You wrong to be with me?
No, you're just old.
Should I be?
Well, it is an emotion.
There haven't been several to me since we started this trek.
Oh, June, don't start imagining things.
I don't have to.
This time I know it's not my fault.
I've done everything I could to please you, and still you avoid me.
You seem to take a sadistic pleasure out of making me miserable.
You know, you're getting in the way of my cigarette.
Don't leave me like a wounded animal to suffer.
You're going to tell me why you've been acting like this.
You're seeing a stealth kitty, aren't you?
Look, I didn't ask to come along here with me.
This was your idea.
Now, you tell me why you're torturing me.
I wasn't aware that I was torturing you. I'm sorry.
Sorry's not enough.
I want candy.
I'm leaving tomorrow with the characters, Paul.
I mean it.
Now I have to get into my hoop skirt.
You can't do that. You don't know how important you are to me.
Your leaving would spoil everything.
Oh, I'm burning with tentativeness.
Well, the shirt's going to look like the Shroud of Turin.
Why can't you always be like this?
Disingenuous, unctuous.
I love you so much, Paul.
There's nothing in the world I wouldn't do for you.
Can I have your endocrine?
Oh, I'd even die for you.
What good would that do?
I want you to live for me.
We'll work together.
When we discover the Nando's secret of rejuvenation...
We'll make an infomercial.
I'll make you young again.
You'll be...
Uh, you got a little something here.
...just as beautiful as you were when we first met.
Oh, how stupid I've been.
We've never met!
Of course I'm important to you.
Hmm?
And you really do need me, don't you?
Where else would you get a guinea pig who can talk?
Who can tell you how she feels?
Honey, please, the Nando's.
How desperate I must have been to listen to your lies.
You're too stupid.
And believe them!
You'll keep their hands off of me.
I'll see you dead before I let you stunt me again.
Ma'am, is everything bakapu'ki in there?
[speaking in foreign language]
Translated means, "Can't run from ugly."
[chuckles]
We'll get her. Bring her back.
What's the matter?
It's June. She's run off.
Oh, good one.
I'm not staying with you either.
It's not funny. I just don't get it.
I wonder if that's a Congo Liam floor.
Thank you.
Wow.
What? I can't hear you. I'm deaf.
[speaking in foreign language]
Well, granted, but I still think we should find her.
Ah, come on, June. I'd look great on you.
Let's follow the scent of Metamucil.
Let's see. I reach speeds of 70.
She goes three miles an hour, and I can't catch her.
[speaking in foreign language]
[screams]
Don't worry, June. It's just the D.T.'s.
No, I'm too salty.
I hate conflict.
Are you okay? How many fingers of scotch am I holding up?
No, no, no, no. It's all right.
Try and get hold of yourself.
Look, the leopards kill, and you are safe.
You're with Peter Allen now.
Come. Come.
Let's get you back to the home.
There's only one trouble with running away.
You always meet yourself when you get there.
Chicken soup for the soul.
Now, come on. Let's get back to camp.
We'll make s'mores.
I'd like to show you some carpet samples, if I may.
Um, Hakuna Matata?
Hey.
Hey, it's Cindy and Steph. Hi, guys.
What's that?
Why, that's our scene over there.
What are we doing here?
For crying out loud.
Gosh.
Oh, please say it's booze. Oh, please. Oh, please. Oh, please.
Oh, please. Please. Please. Please. Please.
Cool. It's a big-screen TV.
And she's gone.
I see. It's a three-room Japanese apartment.
It's Marla's. She had this cane in my office.
Guess she shipped herself here UPS.
(speaking Japanese)
Stop yodeling.
So we're not worried about the lion?
(belches)
Hey, the good humor man.
It's a mirror.
Ah, the elephants have been poaching poachers for a change.
Looks as though your friend Marla met a welcoming committee.
Yes, but her body isn't here.
What worries me is why these bodies are still here.
There are plenty of hyenas and vultures around.
What do you mean?
Something's been frightening the scavengers away.
Marge shot.
Ladoo?
Scott Ladoo?
Should we bury him or check for life or...
Ladoo?
Oh, an early prototype for the snowmobile.
Ladoo.
Okay, ollie ollie oxen free.
Ladoo!
Ladoo, ladoo.
I think we better get back to camp.
I left the belt sander on.
She's a very kinky girl,
the kind you don't bring home to mother.
Ladoo!
I'm gonna bego.
They took the vodka.
What do we do now?
Well, I brought scattergories.
I don't think we're going to have much choice.
Oh, you don't, don't you?
That man a hunt alone?
We'd be dead already if he wanted to kill us.
Hi, I'm from the campground next door.
Could you turn down your radio a little bit?
It's the Earl Cannon Bear tribe.
Do you guys know where the javelin throw is being held?
Give me your gun.
No, give me your pants.
I'm doing it, Shakitsuka.
They got the grain belt.
No.
Oh, my God.
Wouldn't it be great if you were kidnapped
by an African tribe and they brought beer?
Really good beer.
Friends are visiting from Europe.
Meanwhile, thousands of miles away in actual Africa.
Sunny days sweeping up the clouds at night.
And now back to our set.
No justice, no peace.
No.
And don't you dare lift up a tent flap and escape.
He's not that great a white hunter, is he?
He's a pretty crappy white hunter.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
Oh, I guess I'm fine.
This blacktop's really hot.
Sadly, this tribe of extras no longer exists.
They're working themselves up for something.
Thanks, Margaret Mead.
Maybe we're the something.
You don't know how right you are.
I see a huge jar of Mrs. Dash.
Oh, Alberta Hunter's gonna do a striptease.
Oh, my hip.
Oh, God, you're killing me.
Oh, I think we're about to have company.
It's the Mertzes.
Jed!
Close the door.
It's Marla.
She'll help us, you'll see.
Then you'll be sorry.
I hope you're right.
We'll need it.
Miss Jane Pittman and Mr. George Clinton were wed today
in a traditional African-Polynesian Nando's ceremony.
Yeah, in a minute.
That lock always sticks, sorry.
Lady, you don't really have to stoop that low.
I guess Marla is Nando for rawhide chew.
Dr. Talbot, we meet again.
Yes.
I'm expecting you.
Then tell your people to set us free.
We're not here to do harm to anyone.
I've got to go.
I'm not here to do anything.
I've come to help.
I know why you've come.
You're searching for the source of the sacred Nike.
The sacred Nike?
I will show it to you.
An orchid.
A species that grows only in this region of Africa.
Look.
Check it out.
The pollen.
A rare plant.
It takes years to harvest even a few ounces of the pollen.
Then it is aged five years more.
That flower, the plant, they're still alive.
It is too valuable to destroy.
I must have it.
For that one plant and permission to go,
I'll give your people whatever they want.
Money, cattle, guns, anything.
Lakers tickets.
Why in such a hurry to depart?
Didn't I tell you that there was even a greater secret?
Don't you want to see me made young again?
Well...
Of course I do, but I never dreamed it could be possible.
I came here to die.
Oh, I'm dead.
But before the old women of Nando's die,
they receive the final gift of youth again.
Through days of happiness and love,
before they wither to dust.
She looks like Lee Marvin.
The greatest gift that I could give you
would be to let you witness this.
Yes.
If I could see it, I would believe it.
Tonight, you, your wife, and guide...
- This guy? - ...will share the Nando secret.
Then you will sell me the orchid and let us go.
Ah, jump up my butt.
Wow.
So, how's jail treating you guys?
Oops, better go.
Well, that went well.
Have you heard the drums, you Nando?
Sorry.
Man, I really hate how these guys are ripping off David Byrne's music.
Jeez.
We're not as into it as the other guys.
What the hell is this?
Man.
He's got an area rug. Look, look.
Well, that's a white woman in blackface there.
Real Africa.
Hollywood Africa.
Paul Simon's backyard barbecues are getting out of hand.
She dances like a drunk girl at the Blain Brook Bowl.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm waiting for a slow dance.
I don't know what it is. We're all just so restless.
Ricker-racker, firecracker, sis-boom-bah.
Bugs Bunny, Bugs Bunny, rah rah rah.
Spanking machine, spanking machine.
This is nice. Pearl really needed this.
Forgive me, you sagacious and blond lawgiver, but if I may have the liberty...
Get to it, chimp.
Well, it seems...
Scram!
It seems that some of the apes have been saying,
"Well, you haven't actually made any law per se."
And, well, some of them are contending that perhaps you aren't really the lawgiver.
What? Who?
Well, I'm not going to name...
Well, Cheetah and Coco and that proboscis monkey.
Do you like him? I think he's just...
Oh, okay, okay. I'm not going to name him.
Oh, okay, okay. Take this down, Bobo.
Laws, laws, laws, laws.
Okay, the great and mighty and foxy lawgiver does decree that there is to be no parking on Sundays.
Yes, you are very wise, lawgiver.
And no soup with buffet.
Ah, yes it is, ape law.
Now, none of this is set in stone. I'm kidding, of course.
Mike, you guys got any laws you want me to give down here?
Yes! Underwear must be worn while trying on swimsuits.
Oh, I have one.
Oh, oh, oh, and only one person in the booth at a time.
And do not attempt to touch the dancers.
Servo, what were you up to out on the edge of the universe?
All I'm saying, my friend, is will the wolf survive?
Probably not.
Great. Sounds good. Make copies, boo-boo, and CC all the other apes.
What the hell am I supposed to do with these?
Well, you know, the DNR has some good programs.
Look, it's just a metaphor.
The wolf has been reintroduced into Wyoming.
Hey, come on, I'm dark. I'm moving. I might kill myself.
Whoa!
Get in.
Oh, Jesus, guys.
And you, other white man.
I stand up act.
Shiny purple shins.
Batteries are getting low.
Or me.
Getting this, George.
What?
She needs bag bomb.
She's forgetting bingo.
Shut up and get young.
Sum up.
Hi, ma'am.
You will try the French onion soup.
He's drugged.
Now it's time to kiss grandma.
Free inside each specially marked skull.
Ooh, my gym coach used to hit me with one of these.
I would think he'd have lower back problems with a hat like that.
He's not a very good mohel, is he?
He's lance the pineal gland deep in the cerebellum.
Oh, I got stuff on my thing.
Can I get a glass, please? I'm dripping pineal juice here.
Wow, a woman made entirely of gravy skin.
It's Retson. Ding.
He's adding the pineal hormone to the knife.
But she actually ordered a Gibson.
So, yep, she's sending it back now.
Diaries.
Like a stone raging inside you.
Boy, she's just poured into that sarong, isn't she?
Diaries.
Come on, get her some tater skins.
Whoa, I got so hammered at the pineal deal last night, man.
And Agnes Moorehead as Endora.
Fajitas are up.
Huh, well...
Chad...
Clean up in aisle five.
Well, tough luck, girl.
Yeah, could have been any one of us.
So, yeah, want me to box up that pineal juice for you, ma'am?
It's a trick.
It's another woman.
No, no, it's Marla.
It's Janet. Miss Jackson, if you're nasty.
Hi.
Guess who's got it going on?
Uh, it's double bubble, so you get two of them, ma'am.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
This looks suspiciously like Griffith Park to me, huh?
She enjoys snowboarding and playing with her cats.
Miss Ohio!
How am I doing?
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Hi.
Now you have seen the secret of the Nandos, as I promised.
How do we know you're a Marla?
Do you remember the mark of the Arab slaver that I showed you in your office?
I knew I was right.
Yeah, yeah.
Marla, you've got to help me take your secret back to the States.
It is the one secret that will never leave my people.
When I die, you too shall die.
Do you guys know about this?
Until morning, I grant anything you may wish, save freedom.
I wish for a million more wishes.
Marla, could you make my wife young again?
Yes, but she must choose the man for the sacrifice.
I choose Adam Sandler.
Never do that.
Think well before you refuse an opportunity as rare as this.
I will be outside.
When you have made your decision, call me.
I'm at extension 213.
Wow, what are you going to do, honey?
You've got to do this for me.
If you can divert their attention, we may get a chance to escape.
We could get help and come back for you.
Marla, Marla.
The feeling you actually leave me here.
Sure, hell yeah, why not?
Garvey and I can be back tomorrow now that he knows the exact location.
If we get every light, it'll take longer.
I see what you mean.
Tom, I don't mean to butt in, but...
Marla?
Make me hot.
I'm ready.
Come, choose a man for the sacrifice.
Do you have your choice?
Any man I wish?
Any man.
Except Warren Christopher.
Then I choose... him.
Illuminate!
June! Why? This comes completely out of nowhere!
You have made an excellent choice.
Thanks.
You will have beauty and revenge at the same time.
Mrs. Talbot, now that Marla has given you the precious gift of youth,
I think it only fitting you show your appreciation
and give her your beautiful gold necklace.
Don't you remember?
The expensive gold necklace you asked me to keep safely for you?
The exploding necklace?
Oh, yes, I remember.
Marla, would you accept this gift from me?
Since vanity has no regard for time, I will wear your necklace.
Garvey knows exactly where it is.
May he bring it here?
Ama Niza!
Make a hole, people. White man.
You know, you can go overboard on the film noir look.
Garu garu.
So how are you liking the rains here in Africa?
Well, I'm gonna take some time to do the things I never had.
Marla!
Yeah?
Barage.
Marla?
It's from the Mr. T collection.
Marla!
Tare goi?
Whoa!
A couple of A Fuentes Rothschilds here.
Toregos.
Bara.
It's a fruit roll up, see?
Leliamondo.
This guy's the Kramer of East Africa.
Barage.
I'm Ray. Isn't that dynamite? Ray?
Ray.
Get on out there. Tell the guards to bring you back and be rough with you.
Okay? Thanks.
Just gonna grab a handful of tennis bracelets for the wife.
Okay, honey, the joke's over.
Geez.
I'm in a bit of luck.
Well, that opens the pores, eh? Now we'll exfoliate.
I'll just pat you down there. I think you're fine.
Who wants Pinio?
Ay, it is!
Four.
Kill him some more.
There you go.
Look at their god as a mouth breather.
Just dip into my uncle's skull there.
There you go.
You want to light a fire under it, lady? This tusk mask is killing me.
What a sticky wicket.
Come on, it's good for your nails.
Do it.
It's lungy.
This doesn't have any fat in it.
Opa!
Hold on, everyone, that's not the night bae. That's dysentery.
Drizzle, drizzle, drizzle, drome. Time for this one to come home.
He accidentally tapped his pituitary. She's a midget now.
Hello.
Oh, so long, mincing man-pig character. You were enjoyed.
Watch this. She comes out looking like Nancy Culp.
I thought I was Dale.
Is it true?
Kroger's has double coupons?
They turned her into Leni Riefenstahl.
Good shit.
So it gave her a Wonderbra too?
Okay, people, let's clean up. We got two more tomorrow.
She's like a week younger.
Man, her breasts have migrated up to her shoulders.
Next in the spokes-goddess competition.
Here.
Is this your card?
It's my driver's license. What do you think?
I'm young. I'm young again.
Yes. And you're going to stay young.
Right? You better.
We're getting out of here.
M-80s man. Got him in Wisconsin.
Come with me.
Get out there.
Yeah, yeah, keep your loin cloths on.
Yeah, it's good to keep an open mind.
Please get out of my skull.
They have a heat and glow campfire.
I just know Marge is going to want some of this.
Well, better do my number.
Go on.
Scram pal.
Your youth will not last long. Do not waste it.
Go get yourself some nasty.
You know, you have a great time at the Pitial Glands ceremony.
But you still go home alone.
This night is yours.
Go rock someone's world.
The coming day brings you death.
Enjoy it well, both of you.
Enjoy death?
Yeah, fall toward the blast.
They're getting your time?
What?
Yep, they're getting your time.
They're getting your time.
Are you going to do the whole village?
Oh no, the duty free shop.
The menstrual hut.
Well, they needed a new one anyway.
Throws like a girl.
Quick, pray for monsoon.
Typical British reaction, throw dynamite at the problem.
That was really cool, all the huts blew up instead of honey.
It's not stock footage, it's more like stock mileage at this point.
Two cycle alligators.
Sounds like they're running a little rich.
Yeah, I seen Pogo.
Now it's an alligator.
Lyle?
Please tell me, am I an alligator or a crocodile?
We've crossed the county line, he has no jurisdiction.
Ah, we'll just go hang out with Paul Hogan then.
Boy, that wasn't close.
This guy couldn't guide you through a petting zoo.
We are safe as long as we stay away from the river's edge.
That Crispin Glover is creepy.
Do you know where we're going?
Yes I do.
The river runs north all the way to Lake Victoria.
That's where the railroad is.
I don't know.
It will take us quite a while to get there.
Oh, hello.
You're neat.
Oh, Miss Havisham.
Careful, you're laying on a scorpion there.
Look at them.
And Mala said it wouldn't last.
More roast stick, honey?
You know, David, sometimes I can't sleep at night
thinking the way I was.
I'd rather die than go back to bed.
There won't be any going back.
From now on we go sideways.
I took care of that.
Young lady, you're in the company of a man
who's going to be very rich once we get back.
I have here the elixir of sudden wealth and beauty.
You got away with them.
Wasn't that the whole purpose of the expedition?
Ah, ah, ah, you're not poking my pinneal tonight.
Oh, look, he's nivening.
So weird, they portray all men as dumb and driven only by sex.
Hey!
My hand's hot.
Ah, I'm stuck to the ground.
Ugh, slept like a raisin last night.
Jaaaaaaad!
Come on, Pinneal, Pinneal, come on, Huggy Bear, give me some Pinneal.
Wake up and don't look at me.
And you are.
Oh, my hip.
I need the Louis and Vernon catalogue.
I'll call you, I swear.
David, please don't leave me.
You deserve something better than me.
David!
David, don't leave me.
I'm very nurturing and I keep myself in shape.
Oh, damn, rummy quicksand.
But chin up and let's have a sing-song.
Help me out, I'm sinking, King.
Give me the leather poach.
Help me out first, I'll give you the leather poach.
You are the leather poach.
I hope you turn into a baby.
Help me!
June, come on, quick!
I can't get out!
Hurry up, what are you waiting for?
Just putting on my face.
Alright.
Alright, here.
Grab on.
Those coffee grounds are deadly.
If she's grotesque, she's gotta be at least 40.
Oh, damn.
Pineal.
Pineal juice is gonna be all mixed up with pipe tobacco and mud.
Oh, blast, I seem to be dead.
Still, must make the best of it then.
Simply redouble our efforts and grab a lorry and take a lift over to the derby
and things should be all globby by next week.
No problem.
Okay, pretend it's scatch, pretend it's scatch.
Delicious.
Soon, pineal shipment, spam the globe.
Sorry you were in the pound, honey.
That must be June's plane now.
I always get vibes from her landings.
What an awful thing to go through.
Coach, the whole way.
She was crazy about the doctor and he treated her just terribly.
Maybe he had the right idea.
Made sure it worked for him.
Except he's dead.
Don't you try anything like that if you want to stay in one piece.
Don't want to fall against the coffee table again, huh?
Elizabeth Taylor and Nikita Khrushchev.
You know, she's lost control of her hair.
Yeah, she's letting the hair play her.
Yep.
It's Wally Cox.
You see her?
No.
You can't be scared of your own hair.
Why, is it Flight 16?
Maybe she missed the plane.
Or maybe she's young and we won't recognize her.
No customs.
People walking off with green monkeys, giant African termites.
Are you Neil Foster?
No, but I play one on TV.
Yes.
This woman's not with me.
I don't know who she is.
She's my mom, actually.
Have we met?
No.
How do you know my name?
Mrs. Talbot described you in detail.
I'm her niece, Terri Hart.
Well, how do you do?
Here, I never mentioned you.
Is she with you?
No, June came down with the flu.
The 3-2 flu.
She asked me to come ahead and open up the house and get things ready.
Yes.
Oh, you'll be staying with her?
Yes, now that she's alone.
Will you ever be nude?
Oh, would you mind getting my luggage for me?
Then we can go.
Well, you can stay on me, with me if you want.
Excuse me, sir.
Stay in front of your hair, charge your hair, be aggressive, come on.
Absolutely.
I'm Sally Howard.
I used to work for your uncle.
Of the Moe Howards?
Yes, I know.
Oh, then your aunt described me to you, too.
Yes, she did.
She described a popsicle with a bad haircut.
Then she told you that Neil and I are engaged.
She's certainly slut.
I mean, oh, how nice.
No, she didn't mention it.
Why should she?
I don't know.
Just thought I'd mention it.
Is this your bag, the brown one with the blue one?
Is this your bag, the brown one with the pineal juice dripping?
I am Mr. Ed.
I'm going to buy more luggage and fill it and bring it over.
That's everything.
Oh, thank you.
I need you so bad right now.
I hope you'll be comfortable.
Thank you.
If you need anything, why just call me at the office.
And I'll be at the office.
I love you.
Bye, Miss Hart.
Bye.
Neil.
Yes, I love you.
Whipped cream.
Oh, yes, oh, yes, oh, yes.
Remember, my aunt keeps the liquor.
The liquor?
Well, there's never enough to keep.
I can show you some stains by the couch.
Neil, Neil.
Who is that woman in the car?
She keeps it under the bar.
And under the couch and in the toilet tank and a few fake books.
And there's a hollow lamp and hung out a window with a rope.
Neil, Neil, Neil.
What do you have?
You're the bartender.
How about a little vodka over ice?
That's fine.
Only, there isn't any ice.
Next time you come, there will be.
Take me down.
He makes a real good straight vodka.
I had a paper route once.
More liquor?
To your new home.
Cheers.
God, you're so jealous.
I better go.
No problem.
Thanks.
You need any lardone or?
Oh, just one more thing.
Could you provide a map of liquor stores in the area?
Would you mind taking my bags upstairs?
Yes, I'll marry you.
No, glad to.
Thank you, God. Thank you, thank you, thank you, God.
Neil, Neil.
Which room?
Put them in my aunt's room for now.
I don't know what room I'll be using.
But I will be using them.
All right.
I could take all the furniture upstairs if you want me to.
I read the funniest sub-paragraph in the Uniform Commercial Code.
Neil, Neil.
Oh, grandma, decorations make me so hot.
Cover me in doilies and read me Ann Landers.
There's a little stuffy in here.
A lot of back pain with that chair.
It's been closed up for so long.
Neil, Neil, Neil.
Nice view of the fiancé from here.
There.
That's better.
God, emasculating hippo, give me some freedom.
She's getting impatient. I'd better go.
Kiss me like I'm not Eve Arden.
Sally's outside waiting.
That's your skinny ass aunt, Neil.
She's here, skinny-head.
My time is much shorter.
He's some kind of leech lady?
I can't explain that.
You think I'm attractive?
Tell her no. Tell her she's a warthog.
Neil.
And perhaps a little aggressive?
I don't know you well enough to answer that.
Would you like to?
Yeah, I think I would.
Boy, he must need a hand with that luggage or something.
Now she juts.
She enters a room before she does.
Hey, stop eating my eye. Ow!
God.
Get out of here.
What?
Get out.
Whoa!
Guess I misread some signals.
Terry, what's wrong?
Terry!
Just go.
They rolled the tarp out on her face.
Terry, are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
I'm just moulting.
Just go.
Terry, why are you doing monkey noises?
She doesn't want me?
What's her deal?
Hmm.
I realize now what a horrible lie our engagement has been.
I, frankly, feel very disgusted by the thought of...
Oh, hi, honey.
I don't think an explanation will help.
Do you want to try?
Nah, let's go get a burger.
No, I... I don't.
I left you some gum in the car.
I had a drink with Terry and took her bags upstairs.
There was a bushman in the luggage and he attacked.
Look, her aunt's an important client and a good friend.
I... I couldn't just run out.
Now, don't start imagining things.
You know, this is the '50s.
Why am I explaining things to a woman?
Get in the car!
And in closing, we should see other people thanking you in advance for the engagement, etc.
Nipple, hello?
Yes.
Mrs. Talbot?
And why shouldn't I buy light bulbs from the store?
Yes, of course.
I'll send a slice in my pineal gland. Okay.
This is odd. I seem to have a client.
- Drew. - You're busting out all over.
Why didn't you call me? I could have met you at the airport.
I didn't want to bother you.
I... I can't tell you how sorry I was to hear about Paul.
Let's not talk about that.
It's been a nightmare.
Please sit down.
Um, don't be alarmed, but there are two ermine fighting it out on your back, lady.
Well, he belonged to the Stephen King Book Club for a month.
Now, what can I do for you? I want to hear all about your trip.
I'm sorry you were mauled by a tiger.
Shocking, isn't it?
What three months of tragedy can do to a woman.
There's the gallons of vodka, too. That enters into it.
June, I'm... I'm sorry.
Well, I didn't come here for sympathy.
I need money until Paul's insurance can be settled.
Why, of course. Will 500 be enough at the time being?
5,000 would be better.
Why does he have a single meatball in his inbox?
Yes, Greg, will you make out a check, Mrs. Paul Talbot, for 5,000?
That was a complex legal maneuver.
Now, may I please have my jewelry?
Certainly. It's right here.
If I can remember... Three! That's it.
I got a box of army men. You want to play?
(door closes)
Hoyo de Monterey.
June, if there's anything I can do for you, please don't hesitate to call.
I hold ladies' jewelry and that's all I do, but I'm good at it.
I appreciate that.
I'm going to cut off my ear and box it up.
Could you run it over to your niece for me?
Oh, I, uh... I almost forgot.
Thank you for being so kind to my niece.
Oh, that's okay.
(chuckles)
She's hatching eggs, then?
Did she say when she'd be nude?
Oh, that's okay. I got, like, a legal thing to do.
If I see Terry, would you like me to tell her to call you here?
Yes, no matter what time it is, I...
Well, I want to know if she's safe.
Thank you for being so concerned.
(sniffles)
I know she'll appreciate it.
Well, I'll pick up the check on my way out.
I'm billing you hourly for my concern.
She's got the number right.
(door opens)
(door closes)
(beeping)
(door opens)
(chuckles)
Shh. Okay.
Um, Mike?
Yes, O.C. Mike?
I'm putting in my contacts.
We have something really cool to show you, Mike.
Yeah, it's an Adrienne Barbeau calendar, Mike.
(chuckles)
Uh-huh.
And who's she again?
Oh, boy. Well, how about Rhea Perlman?
Sam, no!
What?
Mike, do you like technology?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We have a Conrad Johnson app up here, Mike.
You can see the tubes.
Hungry Mike, Arnie's whole beef half's just delivered.
The Boston Commons is on.
The latest issue of Femme Fatale.
Rick James back from the slammer in a rare acoustic performance.
You guys want me to come up here?
(whispering)
Sure.
Mike, could you come up here?
Yeah, sure.
Gee, thanks, Mike.
That's really nice of you.
Say, could you help us check out our pillory here?
Hey, when did we get one of these?
Oh, uh, before.
Now, just tuck your head in there real nicely, Mike.
Oh, okay, I feel a little silly, but okay.
No! No!
Ow, my contact!
Oh, jeez.
Oh, my God, what happened?
Ah, that could have slammed right down onto your pineal gland,
squirting the precious juice into that beaker.
Then we could have drunk up the precious pineal juice and lived forever.
Oh, but thank God, Mike was safe.
Precious pineal juice still coursing through his glands,
and we get none.
So where's my calendar?
It's up your bucket, you corn-shucking moron.
Ew, I'm from Wisconsin. I don't want to die.
No calendar then, huh?
Beat it.
I'll see you later.
Well then, Gypsy.
Sure, why not, old Gypsy?
Free pictures of Richard Baszler.
Examples of love's baby sock.
Copies of sassy.
Love for sale.
Oh, hi, Peter Lorre as M.
Oh, I love going to bar.
I usually order sandwich and have drink.
Sharky W. Lothario.
Foster Brooks.
Let me pick it up, lady.
I just want to find out if I can bend over without falling down.
See, my pineal gland is over large and sometimes...
Oh.
Oh, Uncle Billy.
Carrying quite a lot, lady.
It ain't safe in this part of town.
Thank you. You're very kind.
Are those real rocks, lady?
May I buy you a drink?
No, thanks. I'm on a wagon.
Oh, Bill W., you imp.
There's not much art in bar.
It's so upsetting to see your grandma trolling.
Mario Cuomo, gigolo.
Couple on way to bar.
She's leaving a slipstream of grandma pheromones.
Desperately poor man's Humphrey Bogart.
Midwest's largest pineal distributor.
Music.
Looking for my little liver pills.
Are you new to city?
Yeah, sure. Bobby and Sissy, yeah, I know 'em.
Myron Florin, personal friend of mine.
That's right. Coffee coupons are my middle name.
Say, in the mood for some meringue?
Hey, what do you say we go home, turn up the thermostat to 85,
and watch a little Matlock, eh?
And then you put those dirty french fried onion rings right on top of it?
That sounds great.
Hey, I can warm up the sitz bath.
Tequila.
There's a million pairs of circulation hosiery of a naked city.
Sorry, I swallowed your bridge work.
Ask me about my grandchildren.
You like music, honey?
Real hot music.
That's not Alan Shepard, is it?
Isn't this a beautiful view?
Yeah.
Just like Tiffany's.
Oh, are we gonna see open-mouth grandma kissing?
Yeah.
You dig young guys, honey?
I like young men very much.
They're so nice. They shovel my snow in the winter.
Where do you come from, honey?
Does that matter? I'm here now.
Nice ou mine. I can get ou mine uptown at cost.
Got new relatives.
Real hot relatives.
Now we're all alone.
He seems trustworthy.
Worry about your mission, huh?
No, that's why I appreciate your company so much.
Let's escape to Branson, you and I's.
You married?
I was once. He's dead now.
Let me 80 billion gedillion.
That's too bad.
Yes.
He was like you in so many ways.
Dead.
How's that, honey?
He was so understanding of older women.
Would you like to dance, sir?
Certainly.
I'm very understanding of you, honey.
Especially in all this beautiful jewelry that you're wearing.
It's from the Sarah Coventry collection.
Now it's hot jazz murder music.
She's in the zone.
She's hitting pineal glands at will.
Inside the pain. Outside the pain.
Dooby dooby doo. He's dead.
So in conclusion, our engagement cannot and will not stand.
I refer you to the attached cottasil.
Obstacle.
Obstacle. I mean...
Sally, what are you doing here?
It'd be more to the point if I asked you,
considering we had a date two hours ago.
Objection. Girlfriend is badgering counsel.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
Is that all you have to say?
Well, I got to working on some briefs. You know.
And I had to write a check. That took a while.
Oh, yes. You've been working.
Very interesting work.
Red hot clients' nieces.
All right. I won't lie to you.
I was with Michael Irvin.
No, wait. That's not...
From Terry?
Sustained.
Hang on. I got to go.
Sally. Sally!
I need to bill you for this time.
(phone ringing)
Oh, jeez.
Hello, Terry Lovers Club.
Terry. How you doing?
Your aunt had me worried. You all right?
Great.
Sure? Yeah, sure.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
In about an hour.
And my glasses will be done?
Bye.
Well, I really should call the governor
about that stay of execution.
Ah, to hell with it.
Always centrifuge your champagne.
Mmm, T.J. Swan, Mellow Nights.
June Cleaver after the divorce.
You could bake a turkey in that dress.
Come in. The door's unlocked.
And so am I.
Hi. Hell hath no fury like me.
Jolene, Jolene, Jolene, Jolene.
Oh, thanks for the love I gave you.
Champagne.
Soft music. Very nice.
Chicken in a biscuit.
You don't miss a trick? I try not to.
Now, why don't you be a good little girl and go on home?
You wouldn't want Neil to find you here like this, would you?
That's for sure.
But you miss the most important thing.
I wouldn't want Neil to find you.
So you're coming with me.
I'm putting you on the next plane to New York.
I've enrolled you in Juilliard.
Ridiculous.
Why don't you get out of here?
This is the most persuasive little instrument,
and if you don't want me to use it, you'd better hurry.
Go right on ahead and take and make my day.
You don't mind if I take my purse along, Leo?
You could survive re-entry in that dress.
And, uh, I'll need a coat.
It's in the hall closet.
Get it?
Women with big ankles love those pants.
And, uh, I'll need to wax my occasional chair.
I just want you to know I'm not putting on a pineal ring.
You're being awfully foolish, you know.
And I can see myself in her butt.
If I did go, I could always come back.
You can see yourself in anyone's butt.
By that time, Neil and I will be on our honeymoon.
That makes our marriage completely inviolable.
You didn't have a lot of trouble this way.
Little girls will play with guns.
All right, one of these.
When two girls fight, who wins?
The American viewing public.
Dear Heloise, I got some pineal juice on my shag rug.
Think about this. This is all about Neil.
Ooh. Think about it.
William Conrad was once stuck to that chair.
Oh, that's a screw-top bottle.
Boy, you really did me a favor killing her.
I can't thank you enough.
I got this at Super America. Red grape malt duck.
I, uh, I told Sally how I feel about you.
Well, I didn't actually tell her yet,
but I'm pretty sure I will, like tonight.
You didn't take it very well.
Came home with a penny a leak.
Everybody can't win.
Like my vinyl hair wash?
I'm just lucky that you want me.
It's a sauna suit.
Would you like to make weight tonight?
Yeah.
Just thinking about you is...
Quit eating my ear.
...insiding.
All she's hearing is "dek-k-k."
This is love.
Love is a many-tepid thing.
I never loved Sally.
Great. Now you've got eyeliner all over your nose.
Terry?
Ugh. He's really into cheek lickings.
Will you marry me?
Uh, uh, I withdraw the question.
Oh, Neil, I can't.
Starfleet forbids it.
Why not?
There are reasons.
What reasons?
Don't you love me?
It's because I love you. I can't marry you.
They could put a spigot on his pinion.
Oh, no, let's not get so serious.
Let's enjoy each other while we can.
Their noses are incompatible.
There's no time like the present, you know.
Man, have I got a torch for you.
Neil, I'm in the Hope chest.
She killed me. Get me out of here.
I'll get it.
Oh, that'll be the trampoline rental place.
Yes? What is it?
Police. Mrs. Paul Talbot in?
No, she isn't. She's spending the night with friends.
From Europe.
What's the trouble?
Mind if I look around?
No, just a minute. This is a private residence.
Unless you have a search warrant.
Just do.
Neil, make them go away.
We're from the transgender society.
Many women like us are struggling.
I'm afraid he has the right to be here.
This is a search warrant.
It's a receipt for a canoe paddle, stupid.
Officer, I'm Mrs. Talbot's attorney.
If she's in any trouble, I have a right to know about it.
Can I say anything about trouble?
Assumed with a search warrant and all there is.
If I knew what Mrs. Talbot is accused of,
maybe I could help.
She isn't accused of anything.
We just want her for questioning about a murder.
Murder?
Did I say anything about murder?
Oh, that's impossible.
Just doesn't figure.
A woman who owns a house like this
getting mixed up with a guy like Jerry Lando.
Who's he?
Small time con man.
No rent rendezvous.
He was found murdered in his car earlier tonight.
Whatchamacook, he pierced.
He was seen in the presence of an elderly lady.
That's horrible.
No witnesses.
Witnesses that could identify Mrs. Talbot?
No need to.
Lando had her calling card in his pocket.
This address, Mrs. Paul Talbot.
This guy's gonna die of nonchalance.
Well, maybe he kidnapped her.
We won't know till we find her.
Is this a supporting beam here?
Lando probably planned to rob her.
That was his specialty.
What kind of varnish do you use?
Got the drop on him.
He was killed with a peculiar sharp instrument.
Why, Aunt wouldn't do a terrible thing like that.
Good, Ant.
I'm gonna do another lap, you mind?
It was a murder exactly like this one a week ago.
Well, not my job to connect him.
Then it couldn't have been Mrs. Talbot.
A week ago, she was in New York.
So it was a murder.
Joe, I guess we better exercise that search warrant.
See if there's anybody upstairs.
I object and stuff.
The witnesses said your aunt was wearing
a large diamond necklace tonight.
Well, that proves it.
Mrs. Talbot's diamonds are right here.
Bad lawyer, damn.
All that proves is that your aunt's
been here since the murder.
All right, where is she?
Well, I don't know.
Anyone upstairs, Joe?
Nobody up there.
I kind of combed it.
I won't let you search this house and lie on top.
All right.
Get away, get away.
No, no, don't open that door.
Don't, don't.
Neat.
Riding in a pool of her own pideal.
This is like a murderous episode of Lucy.
She tried to kill me.
Oh, OK, then that's fine.
I had to kill them.
It was my only chance to stay young.
We really did find the secret if we do.
Because I kept the good thing and the oh boy.
I'll show you.
I'll become beautiful again.
Well, this is great.
She's going to show us.
That lamp looks like the fatted hen.
The Targo theme.
Barbara Stanwyck.
So her hairstyle changed as well.
Well, that's what happens when you buy sure fine pineal juice.
Not working.
I killed Sally for nothing.
Hit it.
Oh, goodbye, my clone Edna.
She destroyed her promotional sized bottle of white shoulders.
No.
It makes no sense.
Why would she jump from such a sumptuous room?
Chad!
She missed the cement pond.
You used to date her.
I can't believe you liked her.
Old Hickory is dead.
Big one.
Chad!
Thanks.
Hey, old mala and young mala were different.
Wait a minute.
Who's Jerry?
Maybe he was one of the Tuskmen.
Good night, everyone.
Old women are evil.
Chad!
Come on, I've been waiting through the whole movie.
You guys promise.
Yeah, but you seem a tad too excited about it.
Yeah, it's really weird.
Oh, come on.
What do I ever ask of you guys?
Nothing.
All I want is this one stinking little Beverly Hillbillies sketch.
What, Mike, you jealous?
Ah, that's it, huh?
You're insane with jealousy because I get to play Granny.
Yeah, you too, crow.
You're jealous too.
Admit it.
Right.
You know, call it nutty, but it seems like you dream this thing up
just so you could run around yelling, "Jed, Jed, Jed."
No, no, not like that, you fool, like this.
Chad!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that, that.
Yeah, it seems to be the whole point of the Enterprise.
Oh, nonsense.
Granny Clampett is a complex and highly nuanced character
with her own integrity.
Well, she doesn't just traipse around the house all day yelling,
"Jed!
Chad!
Chad!"
Oh, come on, you're doing it again.
Yeah, Mike, let's go get us a couple of Hot Pockets.
Yeah, let's do it.
Okay, Nelson, lose the jumpsuit, put on the red plaid and overalls.
Now!
Whoa!
Crow, into your buddy absence.
You know, if we have to do this, I'd really rather be Mr. Dry's job.
Shut up, shut up!
You're Jed!
Jed!
Read the lines, Nelson, read them, read them!
Uh, we found that big ol' elephant of yours, Granny.
Jed!
Um, what seems to be the problem here, Granny?
Get him!
Stop it, Mike!
Stop it!
Okay.
You done?
Yes.
Okay, now.
Make a promise.
All right, now just say it normal.
Jed.
Okay, all right.
Now say it again, come on.
Jed.
Okay.
All right, you're all right, you're all right.
Come on, get up here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, you guys.
I hurt you then and I didn't want to.
I didn't even know what I was doing.
I know.
Everyone okay?
All right, that's all right.
Jed!
No, no, no, no, no.
But they have the rummy call to say we're uncivilized.
Bright, prosperous.
You're bright, isn't it?
Thank you, old boy.
Now look here, bright eyes.
I understand we had an unseemly bit of devolution back there, but that's hardly the case.
But that's hardly the norm around here.
Yes, quite the contrary.
What a crust sandwich, sir.
Delightful.
Now this is how we typically conduct ourselves, you flailing furnace freaks.
Civil as you please.
Oxford tweed.
The high tea.
Fine music.
I'm sure you recognize this lovely melody, the "Palevetsian Dance Number Two" by Borodin.
I rather doubt they do, sir.
Quite, quite, quite.
So the next time you claim that we're uncivilized...
You're pipe, sir.
Yes.
Remember this pithy Beaumont.
I know you are, but what am I?
You're a diaper, sir.
No!
Idiot!
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm so glad they thawed me out.
Take your sandwich, lawgiver?
Why, thank you.
And here's one for you.
Ow!